{
    "subject": "resource/William_Puffer",
    "predicate": "property/residence",
    "object": "resource/Lacombe,_Alberta",
    "human_readable": "The residence of William Puffer is Lacombe, Alberta.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9784576296806335,
            "question": "Is Lacombe the residence of William Puffer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9376509785652161,
            "question": "Is William Puffer's residence in Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.891944169998169,
            "question": "Where in Alberta does William Puffer live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.845321774482727,
            "question": "To what city is William Puffer's residence located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8329246044158936,
            "question": "What is the name of William Puffer's residence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8009902238845825,
            "question": "Where does William Puffer reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6835367679595947,
            "question": "In which province does William Puffer live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6652593016624451,
            "question": "Can you provide the location of William Puffer's home?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5290542244911194,
            "question": "What is the address of William Puffer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5134044885635376,
            "question": "What is the name of William Puffer's town?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The residence of William Puffer is Lacombe, Alberta.",
            "html": "dbpedia_331_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the address of William Puffer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_331_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide the location of William Puffer's home?",
            "html": "dbpedia_331_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which province does William Puffer live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_331_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_331_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_331_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_331_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_331_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_331_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_331_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_331_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_331_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_331_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_331_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* There are multiple documents mentioning William Puffer, a Canadian politician.\n* One document mentions that he was born in Ontario and settled in Lacombe, Alberta (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_331/re-ranker-msmarco/56.txt).\n* Another document mentions that the Puffer house was built and named for William Puffer, who was a prominent businessman and politician (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_331/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt).\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple that:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document `25.txt` mentions that the Puffer house was built and named for William Puffer and he settled in Lacombe, Alberta. This supports the statement that the residence of William Puffer is in Lacombe, Alberta."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}